[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Booker"]}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What do you think of what Cory Booker said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "what", "Cory", "Booker", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, I think Booker is telling the truth about how the American people feel.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "Booker", "is", "telling", "the", "truth", "about", "how", "the", "American", "people", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "I could have been listening to President Obama there, couldn't I?", "question_tokens": ["I", "could", "have", "been", "listening", "to", "President", "Obama", "there", ",", "could", "n't", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you actually believe what you said in those attack ads or do you believe what you're now saying to please Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "actually", "believe", "what", "you", "said", "in", "those", "attack", "ads", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "what", "you", "'re", "now", "saying", "to", "please", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "But private equity per se, do you think it's a force for good or a force for bad for the future -- the immediate future of the American economy?", "question_tokens": ["But", "private", "equity", "per", "se", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "force", "for", "good", "or", "a", "force", "for", "bad", "for", "the", "future", "--", "the", "immediate", "future", "of", "the", "American", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I think private equity on balance creates far more job than it kills.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "private", "equity", "on", "balance", "creates", "far", "more", "job", "than", "it", "kills", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "How does it work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, you go around and ask a lot of people for help and over time you pay it off.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "go", "around", "and", "ask", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "for", "help", "and", "over", "time", "you", "pay", "it", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "TO", ":", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Are you hopeful that given your stoic defense of Bain Capital, Mitt Romney might, you know, step in, wave the debt, as a little token of gratitude?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "hopeful", "that", "given", "your", "stoic", "defense", "of", "Bain", "Capital", ",", "Mitt", "Romney", "might", ",", "you", "know", ",", "step", "in", ",", "wave", "the", "debt", ",", "as", "a", "little", "token", "of", "gratitude", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Look, I would not object to anybody who wants to -- who believes in free enterprise donating to help us pay it off.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "would", "not", "object", "to", "anybody", "who", "wants", "to", "--", "who", "believes", "in", "free", "enterprise", "donating", "to", "help", "us", "pay", "it", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bain Capital"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Is this the Obama strategy, you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "the", "Obama", "strategy", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, it's certainly one of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "certainly", "one", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker"]}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, it was although, you know, I have some empathy for Cory Booker and misspeaking the first time he talked about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "although", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "some", "empathy", "for", "Cory", "Booker", "and", "misspeaking", "the", "first", "time", "he", "talked", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "He didn't misspeak, did he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "misspeak", ",", "did", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, he explained further in his video what he meant.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "explained", "further", "in", "his", "video", "what", "he", "meant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "The problem for the Republicans is that while it's great that Cory Booker did what he did, when you see me interview Newt Gingrich you can see there's a certain local issue, isn't there, which is that Newt hammered Mitt Romney exactly on this point week in and week out often on this show, and now has to sit there with a straight face trying not to laugh saying actually, it's all great, I got it completely wrong?", "question_tokens": ["The", "problem", "for", "the", "Republicans", "is", "that", "while", "it", "'s", "great", "that", "Cory", "Booker", "did", "what", "he", "did", ",", "when", "you", "see", "me", "interview", "Newt", "Gingrich", "you", "can", "see", "there", "'s", "a", "certain", "local", "issue", ",", "is", "n't", "there", ",", "which", "is", "that", "Newt", "hammered", "Mitt", "Romney", "exactly", "on", "this", "point", "week", "in", "and", "week", "out", "often", "on", "this", "show", ",", "and", "now", "has", "to", "sit", "there", "with", "a", "straight", "face", "trying", "not", "to", "laugh", "saying", "actually", ",", "it", "'s", "all", "great", ",", "I", "got", "it", "completely", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, but -- and the truth is, the numbers wore out, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "but", "--", "and", "the", "truth", "is", ",", "the", "numbers", "wore", "out", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker", "Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Mitt Romney had more cash to spend, didn't he, than Newt Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["Mitt", "Romney", "had", "more", "cash", "to", "spend", ",", "did", "n't", "he", ",", "than", "Newt", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "It did, but there's -- if you go back --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "did", ",", "but", "there", "'s", "--", "if", "you", "go", "back", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "And the gap between those two positions in the public estimation, I guess in your own estimation is just so massive, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "gap", "between", "those", "two", "positions", "in", "the", "public", "estimation", ",", "I", "guess", "in", "your", "own", "estimation", "is", "just", "so", "massive", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I think people don't really -- it's hard for people to grasp the -- everything that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "do", "n't", "really", "--", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "people", "to", "grasp", "the", "--", "everything", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "So -- I mean even now are they aware of what happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "--", "I", "mean", "even", "now", "are", "they", "aware", "of", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No, they're not aware.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "aware", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "How intoxicating is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "intoxicating", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Incredibly.", "answer_tokens": ["Incredibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Because you didn't want to hear it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "hear", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Twenty-three?", "question_tokens": ["Twenty-three", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes, I mean, but even -- even before then, at the age of 15, I made my first Olympic team, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "but", "even", "--", "even", "before", "then", ",", "at", "the", "age", "of", "15", ",", "I", "made", "my", "first", "Olympic", "team", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "-- it's -- it's the reality check --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "the", "reality", "check", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marion Jones"]}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What did you learn about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, I -- I -- I realized that -- that my priorities were totally out of whack and that -- that I had to figure out who I was, not Marion Jones, the superstar athlete, the pretty smile, the charm and all that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "realized", "that", "--", "that", "my", "priorities", "were", "totally", "out", "of", "whack", "and", "that", "--", "that", "I", "had", "to", "figure", "out", "who", "I", "was", ",", "not", "Marion", "Jones", ",", "the", "superstar", "athlete", ",", "the", "pretty", "smile", ",", "the", "charm", "and", "all", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Appalling painful though it is, that's the beginning of the moving on process, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Appalling", "painful", "though", "it", "is", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "moving", "on", "process", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "-- and look her in the eye and say, it's true?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "look", "her", "in", "the", "eye", "and", "say", ",", "it", "'s", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Oh, extremely painful, because, you know, she was and still is my biggest support.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "extremely", "painful", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "was", "and", "still", "is", "my", "biggest", "support", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Did you turn to her, having rejected her in the way that you said you did -- what was the moment you turned back to her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "turn", "to", "her", ",", "having", "rejected", "her", "in", "the", "way", "that", "you", "said", "you", "did", "--", "what", "was", "the", "moment", "you", "turned", "back", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Not too long after I -- after I pled guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "too", "long", "after", "I", "--", "after", "I", "pled", "guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Because your mother, I guess, had lived the great highs?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "your", "mother", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "had", "lived", "the", "great", "highs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Was she angry with you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "angry", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "What was the poorest choice your mother thinks you ever made?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "poorest", "choice", "your", "mother", "thinks", "you", "ever", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Well, certainly my decision in men.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "my", "decision", "in", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Why were you attracted to the bad guys?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "attracted", "to", "the", "bad", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I don't know, I think I saw -- I saw something in them that perhaps I was lacking in my childhood.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "think", "I", "saw", "--", "I", "saw", "something", "in", "them", "that", "perhaps", "I", "was", "lacking", "in", "my", "childhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Do you have any relationship with him at all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "relationship", "with", "him", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "So you -- you were craving a kind of father substitute, possibly?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "--", "you", "were", "craving", "a", "kind", "of", "father", "substitute", ",", "possibly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Possibly.", "answer_tokens": ["Possibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Is he still alive, your biological father?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "alive", ",", "your", "biological", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "No, he's passed.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "passed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Did you have any feelings about that when you heard?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "feelings", "about", "that", "when", "you", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Not -- but not having a strong male presence in your life and all the pressure on your mom to bring you up and everything, it can't help, can it?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "--", "but", "not", "having", "a", "strong", "male", "presence", "in", "your", "life", "and", "all", "the", "pressure", "on", "your", "mom", "to", "bring", "you", "up", "and", "everything", ",", "it", "ca", "n't", "help", ",", "can", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "I mean it's like a shark pool, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "like", "a", "shark", "pool", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "But by the time the child is old enough and go off to college, how much protecting can you do?", "question_tokens": ["But", "by", "the", "time", "the", "child", "is", "old", "enough", "and", "go", "off", "to", "college", ",", "how", "much", "protecting", "can", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Let's take another break.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "take", "another", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Can we get there quick, please?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "get", "there", "quick", ",", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "We can get there reasonably quick.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "get", "there", "reasonably", "quick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "And you'd gone from 80,000 dollars a race?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'d", "gone", "from", "80,000", "dollars", "a", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["80,000 dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Your kids went to stay with your family in Barbados, right?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "kids", "went", "to", "stay", "with", "your", "family", "in", "Barbados", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Barbados"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Would you have still won the gold?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "still", "won", "the", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Can I play Devil's Advocate with you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "play", "Devil", "'s", "Advocate", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Is that the honest truth?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "honest", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "That moment, when you hand back the medals and you hear this guy say that about you and that is how you're being branded to America, how did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["That", "moment", ",", "when", "you", "hand", "back", "the", "medals", "and", "you", "hear", "this", "guy", "say", "that", "about", "you", "and", "that", "is", "how", "you", "'re", "being", "branded", "to", "America", ",", "how", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Well, I didn't -- it -- it was tough to hand back the medals, certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "it", "--", "it", "was", "tough", "to", "hand", "back", "the", "medals", ",", "certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "-- what might have been?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "might", "have", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Or is tempted?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "tempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "-- keeping it secret or is tempted to or believes it's the only way they can win a gold medal --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "keeping", "it", "secret", "or", "is", "tempted", "to", "or", "believes", "it", "'s", "the", "only", "way", "they", "can", "win", "a", "gold", "medal", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120521pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "-- there's nobody better to ask, what -- what advice would you give them?", "question_tokens": ["--", "there", "'s", "nobody", "better", "to", "ask", ",", "what", "--", "what", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", ":", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "First of all, think about the consequences of your choices.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "think", "about", "the", "consequences", "of", "your", "choices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]